Finding Aid for the Bignou Gallery Albums, circa 1930s-1940s MS.24
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Album 29: Renoir IV
  - La Passerelle d'Escoyes, 1901
  - Poissy: Le Petit Pont, circa 1898
  - Paysage d'Hiver, 1892-1893
  - Noirmoutiers, circa 1895
  - Sentier en Normandie, 1888
  - Paturage au Bord de la Seine, circa 1890
  - Varangeville, circa 1888
  - Toits de Ferme, 1888
  - La Cagnes, circa 1917
  - Saint Tropez, circa 1899
  - Le Pont de Chatou, 1894
  - Le Chemin de Campagne
  - Les Palmiers, circa 1882
  - Varangeville: La Grande Allee
  - Environs de Talloires lac d'Annect, circa 1894
  - Environs de Pont Aven
  - Pont Aven, 1888
  - Le Mistral, 1888
  - Le Village d'Essoyes, circa 1894
  - [figure on path, 2 paintings]
  - Vue Aux Environs d'Antibes, circa 1889
  - [church]
  - Printemps en Provence
  - [landscape]
  - La Clairi├¿re, 1908
  - Le Grand Arbousier, 1908
  - La Route Ensoleil├®e, 1895
  - La Seine a Chatou
  - [landscape]
  - Le Jardin, circa 1874
  - Le Square de la Trinite, circa 1879
  - La Yole, 1880
  - [landscape]
  - La Plage de Varangeville, circa 1900
  - Environs de Cannes, circa 1900
  - Cagnes
  - Les Bles Murs, Varangeville, 1888
  - [figures in fields, 3 paintings]
  - Alger la Blanche, 1881
  - La Mare ├á Essoyes, circa 1913
  - Interpretation de Corot, 1898
- Album 30: Rouault, Georges, 1871-1958
  - Le Nein, 1937
  - La Marocaine
  - Satan
  - Le Christ at Le Docteur
  - Le Christ aux Bras Levés
  - Le Christ e Le Pauvre
  - Le Christ en Croix
  - Pierrot
  - L'Bouyere
  - L'Italienne
  - Le Clown, 1932
  - Pierrot a La Collerette
  - La Figurante
  - Le Suaire
  - Carlotta
  - Le Clown a la Table
  - Les Deux Danseuses, 1932
  - La Petite Servante
  - Antonio
  - Soliel Couchant en Orient, circa 1930
  - Christ
  - Fille de Cirque
  - Carmencita
  - Bouquet de Fleurs, 1932
  - Pommes,1932
  - Pierrot a la Rose, circa 1936
  - Danseuse et Clowns
  - Portrait de A. Vollard, 1925
  - [bust]
  - [three figures]
  - Les Trois Juges, circa 1930
  - La Plume Blanche, 1928
  - Le Reposoir, circa 1937
  - [figures, 2 paintings]
  - Pierrot a la Rose
  - Trois Clowns
  - Clown in Interior
  - Le Vase de Fleurs, 1926
  - [portraits, two paintings]
  - Antinea
  - [figure]
  - Femme Nue Debout
  - Les Trois Juges, 1928
- Album 31: Seurat, Georges, 1859-1891
  - Tete de Jeune Fille, 1880
  - Le Casseur de Pierres, 1884
  - [man lying on ground]
  - [horses in water]
  - [man fishing]
  - La Sieste au Bord de L'Eau
  - Le Pont Bineau, 1885
  - Courbevoie
  - La Perissoire, 1884 or 1888
  - [boats]
  - Andromede, 1880
  - Le Pecheur, 1883
  - Etude pour L'Ile de la Grande Jatte, 1884
  - [people in a park]
  - Au Concert European
  - La Maison Hantee
  - Fort de la Halle
  - Silhouette de Femme
  - Femme Tricotant, 1882
  - Etude pour la Baignade
  - [shoreline and boats]
  - L'Homme A Femmes, circa 1887
  - Ile de la Grande Jatte, 1884
  - Etude de Personnages pour L'Ile de la Grande Jatte
  - L'Ile de la Grande Jatte - La Femme a l'Ombrelle
  - L'Ile de la Grande Jatte, 1886
  - Le Saint Cyrien
  - La Femme au Singe
  - Femme a la Promenade
  - Etude pour la Baignade
  - Etude pour la Baignade, 1885
  - Le Bec de Hoc a Grandcamp, 1886-1887
  - La Baie de Grandcamp, 1885
  - Paysen Assis dans un Pre, 1883
  - Les Trois Maisons
  - Port en Bessin, 1888-1889
  - Le Vase de Fleurs
  - Entree du Port D'Honfleur, 1886 or 1888
  - La Parade, 1887-1888
  - [boats]
  - Port en Bessin
  - Blé et Arbres, circa 1882
  - L'Ile de la Grande Jatte, 1884
  - Port en Bessin, 1888
  - Le Port de Gravelines, 1888
  - Le Pont de Courbevoie, 1886-1887
  - [man and woman with umbrella]
  - [landscape]
  - [figures and horse]
  - [boats]
  - Quai a Honfleur
- Album 32: Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de, 1864-1901
  - [horse, rider, hounds]
  - Aristide Bruant aux Ambassadeurs, circa 1893-1894
  - Portrait du Poete G.H. Manuel, 1891
  - L'Accroche-couer, 1889
  - [woman in bed], 1898
  - La Goulue au Moulin Rouge, 1892
  - La Goulue et son Cavalier au Bal du Moulin-Rouge, 1891
  - Maxime Dethomas au Bal de L'Opera, 1896
  - Le Deux Amies, 1892
  - Le Deux Amies, 1894
  - Alfred la Guigne, 1894
  - La Visite, 1894
  - La Loge
  - Enfant avec la Chienne Pamela, 1900
  - Le Ballet, 1885
  - A la Mie
  - Madame Misia Natanson, 1897
  - Au Cafe
  - Au Moulin Rouge, 1892
  - Jeune Femme dans un Jardin, 1891
  - Femme Nue Etende sur un Divan, 1897
  - Cavaliers se Rendant au Bois de Boulogne, 1888
  - [still life]
  - Casque d'Or, 1891
  - A l'Elysée-Montmartre, 1887
  - Danseuse dans sa Loge, 1885
  - M. Fourcade, 1889
- Album 33: Utrillo, Maurice, 1883-1955
  - Eglise à Stains, 1926
  - Chateau sous la Neige, 1914
  - Eglise à Lucenay - La Rue
  - Chartres, 1912
  - Place de l'Eglise à Bièvres, circa 1918
  - Montmartre, Le Rendez-Vous de Chase d'Henri IV, 1912
  - Montmartre La Rue des Saules, 1914
  - Le Parc Monceau, circa 1912
  - La Viosne à Pontoise, circa 1912
  - Rue Hautefeuille, College Danville, La Tourelle, 1912
  - Basilique de Saint-Denis, 1910
  - Notre Dame Dorée, 1911
  - [Street scene, two paintings]
  - L'Hotel du Tertre, 1912
  - Place du Tertre
  - La Rue Becquerel ├á Montmartre
  - [Street scene]
  - L'Usine, 1915
  - [Street scene, two paintings]
  - Saint Antoine de Padoue
  - La Rue du Mont Cenis
  - Rue a Groslay
  - [Street scenes, nine paintings]
  - La Rue de Paris a Sannois
  - [Street scenes, three paintings]
  - Puteaux, 1914
  - [Street scene]
  - Notre Dame de Paris, 1912
  - [Street scenes, two paintings]
  - Gargenville, Rue de la Mairie, 1912
  - Nanterre, Rue Gambetta, 1912
  - Le Jardin de Montmagny, 1911
  - Souvigny, La Grand'Place, 1912
  - Mantes, L'Eglise Notre Dame des Bles, 1912
  - Eglise a Saverne, 1912
  - Une Rose a Corte, 1912
  - A la Tourelle, Rue du Mont Cenis, 1911
  - La Rue Marcadet, 1912
  - Rue ├á Sannois, 1912
  - Montreuil, La Citadelle, 1911
  - Argenteuil, La Grande Rue, 1912
  - [Street scenes and windmills, 8 paintings]
  - Caserne Parisienne, 1914, 1914
  - Paris: Le Bal Musette, Place de la Contrescarpe, 1911
  - [Street scene]
  - La Caserne a Courbevoi, circa 1914
  - [Street scenes, two paintings]
  - Rue au Conquet, 1913
  - La Maison Rose
  - Puteaux
  - [Street scenes, five paintings]